If you don't want to become bald then do
not bathe in this water of Dehradun.  While
drying my hair after taking bath, I looked down and saw that half of my
hair was lying on the ground.  Due to this tension, I
go to the kitchen and make coffee for myself
and then while drinking coffee, an
idea comes to my mind.  So I quickly go to the kitchen.
But then
what are you doing?
Hey, this water is ruining my hair.  So I am
calling the brother from Na Aro to get this checked.
Yes friend, my hair is also falling.   The
brother from Aaro will come after two-three hours
and then we will get this water checked by him to see what
its TDS level is.  But till then I
empty this swimming pool of mosquitoes collected in the pots.  I was sitting comfortably and
waiting for my brother.  Then this makeup
artist says let's try this viral
ice cream cross from Instagram.  Brother,
this was number one in the test.  So you guys
must also try it.  Then the brother from Aaro
also arrives.  So first I get my RO
serviced from them and then I get the
water coming from the meter checked.  When its
TDS level was seen, it was 263 which is
not even suitable for bathing and people use it for drinking.
Then I
checked the water in the house tank and it was even higher at
280.  See, I was saying that the problem is with the water.
Why did you call him?
You say that the water in the tank is fine.
Because of this we will become bald.  Now I will take a
bath with it.  He is such a big Nawab that he will
take bath in this water.  If you bathe with this water, I will break your legs.